chrome.com 2006-12-07

# Chrome Systems Inc. | Privacy

|   

_This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Chrome Systems Inc.("Chrome") websites, including www.chrome.com, www.webcarbook.com, www.chromeautobuilder.com, and www.chromecarbook.com (the "Sites")._

**Information Collection and Use**

Chrome is the sole owner of the information collected on its Sites. We do not sell, share, or rent your name, street address, phone number, or email address ("Personally Identifiable Information") to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Chrome collects information from you at different points on our Sites. Chrome may release information, including Personally Identifiable Information, when such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law and otherwise as set forth in this statement. 

There are times when we may use a form to request information from you (like your name and address). This information is used to help Chrome and our business partners to fulfill requests for price quotes or other information about a vehicle. This information is normally used to contact you by telephone or email. You will not be contacted if you do not provide any contact information.

Chrome does not control and has no liability with respect to content which is incorporated from a framed site (a website operated by another entity whose material is presented in a browser window frame along side material from our Sites). Use of such content may be subject to other terms and conditions imposed by the operator of such site. Chrome's privacy policy does not apply to information that may be collected by such third party sites. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to your Personally Identifiable Information, though a cookie may contain a user zip code, while on our Sites. User zip codes are not considered Personally Identifiable Information. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates in 24 hours. Cookies allow us to tailor information to your needs. For instance, by accepting a cookie on our Sites, you do not have to log in or follow a series of links more than once, thereby saving time while on our Sites. If you reject the cookie, our Sites may not function properly. Some of our business partners use cookies on our Sites. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Sites, track user movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information and are not themselves considered Personally Identifiable Information. 

We will share aggregated demographic information about users of our Sites with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information that can identify any individual person. We partner with other companies to provide specific services (such as fulfilling a request for a quote on a vehicle). When you request these services, we will share your contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services to you. We ask that our business partners use contact information only for the purpose of providing these services. 

Our Sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Chrome is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave any of our Sites and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects Personally Identifiable Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our Sites. 

We take seriously the protection of your Personally Identifiable Information. We have security in place to protect your information as it exists, both online and off-line. Access to all of our users' Personally Identifiable Information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, web operations manager) are granted access to Personally Identifiable Information. If you have any questions about the security at our Sites, you may send an email to [**securityconcerns@chrome.com**](mailto:securityconcerns@chrome.com).

All information, including Personally Identifiable Information, collected through our Sites is considered a trade secret of Chrome. As the owner of such information, we may disclose or sell such information as an asset of the company in conjunction with the sale to a third party of our company or a portion of our assets. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes here. Continued use of the Sites by you will constitute acceptance of the revised statement. However, with respect to our financial institution clients, we will continue to meet our commitments under the paragraph headings "Sharing" and "Security." Chrome will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy statement and will take prompt corrective action when it learns of any failure to comply with its privacy statement. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, Chrome does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy statement. Chrome shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy statement. 

If you have questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, you should contact: 

Privacy Policy Group  
Chrome Systems Inc.  
700 NE Multnomah, Suite 1500  
Portland, OR 97232  

|
